[
  {
    "type": "intro",
    "pretext": "You’ve learned dakuten (゛) and handakuten (゜)! Awesome! Take this test to see how much you remember. You don’t have to take this test right now if you’re not ready."
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ga and Za",
    "options": ["が and ざ", "が and ご", "ご and ざ", "ぞ and ぐ"],
    "answer": "が and ざ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gi and Ji",
    "options": ["ご and じ", "ぐ and ず", "ぎ and じ", "が and ざ"],
    "answer": "ぎ and じ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gu and Zu",
    "options": ["ぐ and づ", "げ and ぜ", "ご and じ", "ぐ and ず"],
    "answer": "ぐ and ず"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ge and Ze",
    "options": ["ざ and が", "げ and ぜ", "ご and ぞ", "ぢ and び"],
    "answer": "げ and ぜ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Go and Zo",
    "options": ["ご and ぞ", "ぱ and ぴ", "だ and ば", "ご and が"],
    "answer": "ご and ぞ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Da and Ba",
    "options": ["だ and び", "ド andぼ", "だ and ば", "ぼ and ご"],
    "answer": "だ and ば"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Dji and Bi",
    "options": ["び and ぶ", "ぼ and ば", "ぢ and び", "ぶ and づ"],
    "answer": "ぢ and び"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Dzu and Bu ",
    "options": ["ぷ and が", "ぽ and ご", "ど and ぼ", "づ and ぶ"],
    "answer": "づ and ぶ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "De and Be",
    "options": ["で and ぼ", "で and ぽ", "で and べ", "で and ど"],
    "answer": "で and べ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Do and Bo",
    "options": ["ど and ぼ", "ぼ and ぐ", "ず and ぞ", "ど and ぷ"],
    "answer": "ど and ぼ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Pa and Pi",
    "options": ["ぱ and ぽ", "ぷ andぴ", "ぱ and ぴ", "ぴ and ぽ"],
    "answer": "ぱ and ぴ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Pu and Pe",
    "options": ["ぷ and ぽ", "ぺ andぱ", "ぱ and ぴ", "ぷ and ぺ"],
    "answer": "ぷ and ぺ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Po",
    "options": ["ぱ", "ぺ", "ぽ", "ぷ"],
    "answer": "ぽ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Hiragana",
    "options": ["かぞく", "ひらがな", "かたかな", "えんぴつ"],
    "answer": "ひらがな"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Jikan (Time)",
    "options": ["かぞく", "でんわ", "ばす", "じかん"],
    "answer": "じかん"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Kazoku (Family)",
    "options": ["でんわ", "かぞく", "じかん", "えんぴつ"],
    "answer": "かぞく"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Denwa (Telephone)",
    "options": ["でんわ", "かぞく", "じかん", "まずい"],
    "answer": "でんわ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Buta (Pig)",
    "options": ["ばす", "ぱん", "おい", "ぶた"],
    "answer": "ぶた"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Basu (Bus)",
    "options": ["ぱん", "ぶた", "ばす", "ぴざ"],
    "answer": "ばす"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Pan (Bread)",
    "options": ["ぱん", "ぴざ", "ばす", "ぶた"],
    "answer": "ぱん"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Enpitsu (Pencil)",
    "options": ["ひらがな", "えんぴつ", "かたかな", "べんとう"],
    "answer": "えんぴつ"
  }
]